https://buildingproducts.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Building Products Limited holds information to ensure business can be conducted. Building Products Limited is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected in accordance with the law. We take privacy and your rights as an individual seriously.
This policy is produced to provide visitors, subscribers and advertisers relevant information in respects of maintaining your personal privacy. This policy explains how we collect personal data, when we collect personal data and why we collect personal data.
Building Products Limited is the data controller. Building Products Limited is based at 502 Worle Park Way, Weston-Super-Mare, BS22 6WA and is contactable via telephone on 0203 096 2861 or via email at team@buildingproducts.co.uk. Building Products Limited is responsible to ensure your rights as an individual are respected and clear. If you have any queries, please do not hesitate to contact us.
Building Products Limited processes the minimal amount of personal information required to ensure the service you wish to obtain can be provided in the most efficient way possible. We may collect your data via our website, publicly available sources or when you speak directly to a member of the Building Products Team. In order to process your request, we may ask for;
– Contact name(s)
– Company name
– Company address
– Email address
– Company telephone number(s)
All information collected is freely given to Building Products and is only used for the purpose of processing your request as stated. The data is processed using Legitimate Interest.
The information provided is stored in a secure environment within our accounting software and within a CRM environment with strictly controlled access via a web browser with SSL (Secure Socket Layer) protection and encrypted passwords, with daily encrypted back-ups. The servers that hold data are maintained and patched regularly against threats.
The personal data provided is only accessed by the internal team at Building Products Limited and can only be accessed for legitimate reasons. Your data is not shared with anyone outside of the EEA.
The terms of this privacy policy are reviewed every 12 months or sooner if required to keep up to date with any changes in data collection and any technological changes. This document was last updated on the 20/06/2019.
If at any point you feel we are being unfair or dismissing your rights as an individual, please contact us and let us know. If you are still not satisfied, you can make a complaint to a supervisory authority, the ICO. To make a complaint please visit the ICO website at: https://ico.org.uk/
It is important that you understand what your rights are as an individual.
RIGHT TO ERASURE
You may request that Building Products Limited erases your personal data and we will do so within 24 working hours. To avoid the possibility of re-adding your personal data again in the future, we will retain your name and email address (if available). You may request that we add your personal data back on to the database at any time.
RIGHT TO REQUEST RECTIFICATION
If you determine that the personal data we hold about you is incorrect you have the right to request rectification. We will immediately consider the request and rectify any errors found. If we do have reasons to believe that an error has not occurred, we will keep the information as previous. You will be informed of the outcome by telephone, email or post.
SUBJECT ACCESS REQUEST
At any point, you have the right to submit a Subject Access Request. We will respond to the request made within one month. We will not charge a fee for any of the requests above unless the request is ‘manifestly unfounded or excessive’. We also reserve the right to withhold personal data if disclosing it would ‘adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others’.
If you have any queries regarding how your data is held, processed or shared including activating your right to erasure please contact Building Products Ltd, 502 Worle Park Way, Weston-Super-Mare, BS22 6WA, via telephone 0203 096 2861, or via email at team@buildingproducts.co.uk.
ABOUT Building ProductsBuilding Products Magazine launched in 1976 and is the UK’s leading source of product information for specifiers, quantity surveyors, and the construction supply chain.FOLLOW US
Privacy Policy
Contact
© Business Leader Ltd, 2020 | All rights reserved
